[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To which animal class do octopuses belong?", "correct_answer": "Cephalopod", "incorrect_answers": ["Mollusk", "Coleoid", "Nautiloid"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which actor said the line Lets do it for Johnny!?", "correct_answer": "Matt Dillon in The Outsiders", "incorrect_answers": ["Ed Harris in Radio", "Uma Thurman in Johnny Be Good", "Gene Hackman in Hoosiers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does Adolf Hitler do to Dr. Jones Grail Diary in the movie The Last Crusade?", "correct_answer": "He autographs it.", "incorrect_answers": ["He burns it.", "He keeps it.", "He never sees or touches it."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which type of cat is almost always female?", "correct_answer": "Calico", "incorrect_answers": ["White", "Persian", "Siamese"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What month has the garnet for its birthstone and the snowdrop for its birth flower?", "correct_answer": "January", "incorrect_answers": ["April", "March", "February"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Pot Marigold, a.k.a. Calendula, used for in the past, apart from medicinal purposes?", "correct_answer": "As a dye", "incorrect_answers": ["As fertilizer", "As fodder", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first rule of eye make-up is that you can never wear enough blue eyeshadow is a quote from which film?", "correct_answer": "My Girl", "incorrect_answers": ["High School Musical 2", "Hair Spray", "High School Musical"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where was actor Thomas Lennon born?", "correct_answer": "Chicago", "incorrect_answers": ["Virgina", "Florida", "New York"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the Crimean war, which lasted from 28 March 1854 until 1856, an alliance of the United Kingdom, France, the Ottoman Empire and Piedmont-Sardinia fought against which country?", "correct_answer": "Russia", "incorrect_answers": ["Germany", "Italy", "Austria"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Malone, Scott Wilson plays the part of Paul Barlow, the mechanic who is being pressured to sell out by Devaney. Wilson has also played Sam Braun in 9 episodes of this crime show drama.", "correct_answer": "CSI: Crime Scene Investigation", "incorrect_answers": ["NYPD Blue", "N C I S", "Law and Order SUV"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This concept, developed by Alfred Hitchcock, is described as a plot device that motivates the characters and advances the story.", "correct_answer": "The MacGuffin", "incorrect_answers": ["The MacPhail", "The Catalyst", "The Plot Twister"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is a real award?", "correct_answer": "The Ig Nobel Prize", "incorrect_answers": ["The Poly Pulitzer Prize", "The Niagara Falls Literature Award", "The Academic Academy Award"]}]